Today, we are going to make a drawing of an onion line.
How to make an onion line in Claw?
First, we draw a rectangle with a ruler.
The length and width can be decided by yourself.
Next, we draw an inner line in the middle.
The length of the inner line is 15 cm.
We click on it and right-click.
Then we can enter its length and click OK.
Double-click to end.
We can make small lines on the top of the line.
The length of the inner line can be made into a triangle.
We may be able to draw a rectangle with a slightly larger line.
Then divide the inner line into two.
After a division is made, the inner line is divided into two.
Then we will repeat the same process.
We draw two lines on the top of the line.
The length here can be adjusted to 5 mm, and then click on all, then the left and right are available, and then click to confirm.
But after it is generated, there will be a basic line above, you can delete the basic line and select it.
Here, because I don't need a basic line, I can delete it, and we can also generate a vertical line at the same point.
Vertical to the Y-axis, and then the same one is 45, and then click on all, left and right.
OK, delete the basic line again.
Next,
let's repeat it again.
Vertical to the Y-axis, and then the angle is 90 degrees, because what I want is a vertical Y-axis.
Then this is 5 mm, and then there is all, and then there are left and right.
After drawing like this, we are going to adjust the shape of the onion.
The shape of the onion, you first draw it with the internal line, connect it,
and then we are going to adjust the shape of the onion.
Then we are going to adjust the shape of the onion.
Next, this line here, I accidentally press the mouse button
It will become such a curve if it is not long.
If I don't want this kind of curve, then you press Esc to exit and then click directly.
Just pull it over, double shift and finish.
Because of meniscus, if you press the mouse button and left-click, it will pull out such a curve.
When you press the mouse button and left-click and don't put it, you will pull out such a curve.
Then I can exit it by pressing Esc.
Next, I want to adjust the shape of this curve, then you can use the
click curve point or click circle, then here I use the click curve point
to adjust its shape.
If you want the shape to be basically similar to the one that may be exactly the same, then you can put the mouse here,
and then you can add this pattern to it.
Then, the size is adjusted to be similar, you can use the click curve tool,
then you can enlarge this pattern,
it may be a little bigger, a little smaller,
OK,
then now it's almost the same.
In this case, you can use the click curve tool to adjust its shape.
Then you can adjust it slowly, you can add points to it or reduce points to adjust its shape.
If this is OK,
then you can do this,
if you want to delete this pattern,
then you can right-click and rewrite it.
That's fine.
After adjustment, we can use the edit stages to select this line,
and then right-click, it has a copy as mirror, copy as mirror inside line,
then you click it, and then you select the mirror line you want to mirror,
it can be безобtó的进行输入了。
Then the following is the same.
Then select these two lines and right-click to select them.
You see it has changed, you see it looks good.
and then select it, OK, then the following is the same, you can select these four lines
and then right-click to copy the inner line of the mirror and select the basic line of the mirror
OK, then the upper line can be solved in this way, then the left and right, you can choose it, frame it
, of course, when you frame it, you can delete these lines first
, you can delete them all, and then these are the empty points, which means that they are two broken points. If you don't want the empty point, you can choose it. After that, right-click on it
, merge the refraction points with it, and then right-click on it to convert it to a free line point. It's the same here
.
Then after converting it to a free line point
, you can choose between these two lines and then
right-click, there is a copy then right-click it has a paste
paste when you press the SHIFT key, it is delete
At the same time, click on the right mouse button to fill in the Android Shift key.
Then here you can enter a specific size, for example, 100 mm.
Because its next circle is 100 mm, click OK.
That's it.
Then the top and bottom, the top and bottom of the current one, you can also copy the right key and paste the right key.
Then you can also press the Android Shift key, press the Android Shift key, and then you can enter 300.
Because it has a circle of 300, click OK to confirm.
That's it.
Then you can copy all of this here, paste it, and press the Android Shift key.
Then click the right mouse button to enter 300, confirm, OK.
You can frame it like this.
Then Ctrl C, Ctrl V, and then press the Android Shift key.
Here,
you can directly enter the value of 200.
Then Ctrl C, Ctrl V, and then enter the value of 400 directly.
Then the onion horizontal line is done.
If you don't want this point, you can overlap it all.
Just type in the mouse button.
This is the desired value.
Then, I'll check what it is, click OK.
It will be gray.
Yes, now it is gray, so that's it.
This is the room, and then I also press Ctrl C.
This time I'm a little bit more to the right, press 0.
All right, this is it, let's to do it one by one.
So as you can see here, the middle 중 regional buttons.
This is this window.
Okay, let's open it up here. I can add a row to it and stick it on top of it.
Then we set a pressure for it. This is the positive pressure. For example, I set it to be a little bigger.
Then set a negative pressure here. Then let's simulate it.
Because the particle diameter is relatively large, wait a minute, I'll cancel it.
Then we give it a row of fixed points below.
Then simulate it again, you can see it.
Ok, I just wrote it. This is the negative 10, and this is the 10.
Then let's simulate it again, you can see it.
I just wroteпервых, this is theığ value, I can start the effect.
This is the effect of the onion.
This concludes the production of our onion aerial string.
Thank you for watching.